Register of the John Davis Lodge papers, 1886-1987
Hoover Institution Archives
- Interim Years (1961-1969) File, 1954-1969, 1976 (Boxes 117-186)
  - Correspondence, 1954-1969
    - Cassedy, Anthony, 1961 (Box-folder 137: 10)
    - Castiella, Fernando, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 137: 11)
    - Cefaratti, Anthony J., 1966 (Box-folder 137: 12)
    - Chamber of Commerce, Borough of Queens, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 137: 13)
    - Champlain College, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 137: 14)
    - Chandler, Alpheus, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 137: 15)
    - Chapuis, Jane, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 137: 16)
    - Chase, Lucia, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 137: 17)
    - Church, Edgar, 1965 (Box-folder 137: 18)
    - Citizens Anti-Communist Committee of Connecticut, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 137: 19)
    - Citizens for Freedom, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 137: 20)
    - Clark, Ana, 1966 (Box-folder 137: 21)
    - Clark, Charles M., Jr., 1964 (Box-folder 137: 22)
    - Clark, Charles P., 1961 (Box-folder 137: 23)
    - Clifford, Arthur, 1963 (Box-folder 137: 24)
    - Colby-Stilson, Germaine, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 137: 25)
    - College Concert Foundation, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 137: 26)
    - Conant, Luther, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 137: 27)
    - Conant and Company, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 138: 1-2)
    - Connecticut Committee for Captive Nations, 1968 (Box-folder 138: 3)
    - Connecticut Humane Society, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 138: 4)
    - Connecticut Republican Citizens Committee, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 138: 5)
    - Connecticut Republican Finance Committee, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 138: 6)
    - Connecticut Republican Labor League, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 138: 7)
    - Connecticut Research Commission, 1968 (Box-folder 138: 8)
    - Connecticut State Labor Council, 1965 (Box-folder 138: 9)
    - Connell, Arthur, 1962 (Box-folder 138: 10)
    - Conner, Gerta, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 138: 11)
    - Coote, Albert, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 138: 12)
    - Cotton, Helen, 1968 (Box-folder 138: 13)
    - Coutant, Frank, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 138: 14)
    - Cowles, Gardner, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 138: 15)
    - Crane, Kent, 1969 (Box-folder 138: 16)
    - Crittenberger, Willis, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 138: 17)
    - Crockett, William, 1965 (Box-folder 138: 18)
    - Cronan, Carey, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 138: 19)
    - Danenberg, Leigh, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 138: 20)
    - Davis, Fitzroy, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 138: 21)
    - De Bearn, Gaston, 1969 (Box-folder 138: 22)
    - Deegan, Thomas, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 138: 23)
    - DeGray, Edward, 1965 (Box-folder 138: 24)
    - Dempsey, John, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 138: 25)
    - De Streel, Quentin, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 138: 26)
    - Deutermann, H. T., 1965 (Box-folder 138: 27)
    - Dewart, Thomas, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 138: 28)
    - Dewey, Thomas E., 1963-1964 (Box-folder 138: 29)
    - Dirksen, Everett, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 138: 30)
    - Disney, Walt, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 138: 31)
    - Dohanas, Steven, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 138: 32)
    - Donovan, Stanley, 1963 (Box-folder 138: 33)
    - Douglas-Hamilton, Natalie, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 139: 1)
    - Drouin, Jacques, 1962 (Box-folder 139: 2)
    - Duke, Angier Biddle, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 139: 3)
    - Dulles, Mrs. Allen, 1969 (Box-folder 139: 4)
    - Dymkoski, Leo, 1969 (Box-folder 139: 5)
    - Eames, Hamilton, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 139: 6)
    - Easter Seal, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 139: 7)
    - Eisenhower, Dwight D., 1961-1969 (Box-folder 139: 8)
    - Ellinger, John, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 139: 9)
    - Elliott, Lisbeth, 1967 (Box-folder 139: 10)
    - Ellis, Thomas, 1961 (Box-folder 139: 11)
    - Ellsworth, Robert, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 139: 12)
    - Elston, Dorothy A., 1969 (Box-folder 139: 13)
    - Escribano, Fernando, 1966 (Box-folder 139: 14)
    - Escribano, Mariano, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 139: 15)
    - Etting, Emlen, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 139: 16)
    - Evans, Duane, 1966 (Box-folder 139: 17)
    - Evans, Thomas, 1968 (Box-folder 139: 18)
    - Fairbanks, Douglas, Jr., 1966-1969 (Box-folder 139: 19)
    - Fairfield County Hunt Club, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 139: 20)
    - Fairfield County Republican Women's Association, 1961 (Box-folder 139: 21)
    - Faris, Barry, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 139: 22)
    - Farley, James, 1967 (Box-folder 139: 23)
    - Farr, Donald, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 139: 24)
    - Federation of French Alliances, 1966 (Box-folder 139: 25)
    - Feisal, Alfred, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 139: 26)
    - Ferne, Henry, 1963 (Box-folder 139: 27)
    - Field, David, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 139: 28)
    - Field, John, 1964 (Box-folder 139: 29)
    - Fielding, Temple, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 139: 30)
    - Filosa, Gary F., 1961-1969 (Box-folder 140: 1)
    - Findley, Paul, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 140: 2)
    - Fish, Hamilton, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 140: 3)
    - Flanigan, Peter, 1969 (Box-folder 140: 4)
    - Ford, Gerald, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 140: 5)
    - Forsberg, Beatrice, 1963 (Box-folder 140: 6)
    - Forte, Ralph, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 140: 7)
    - Fox Club, 1954-1968 (Box-folder 140: 8-9)
    - Fraleigh, William, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 140: 10)
    - Francoeur, Philip, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 140: 11)
    - Frazer, Peter, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 140: 12)
    - Frelinghuysen, Matilda, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 140: 13)
    - Frelinghuysen, Peter, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 140: 14)
    - Friedman, Irwin, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 140: 15)
    - Friedman, Zac, 1964 (Box-folder 140: 16)
    - Frisby, Owen, 1965 (Box-folder 140: 17)
    - Fulton, James, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 140: 18)
    - Gabard, Pierre, 1965 (Box-folder 140: 19)
    - Gardiner, Jack, 1967 (Box-folder 140: 20)
    - Garibaldi, V., 1962-1967 (Box-folder 140: 21)
    - Garrigues, Antonio, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 140: 22)
    - Gates, Thomas, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 140: 23)
    - Gelardin, Albert, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 140: 24)
    - Gengras, Clayton, 1969 (Box-folder 140: 25)
    - Gerety, Pierce, 1965 (Box-folder 141: 1)
    - Gimbel, Bernard, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 141: 2)
    - Ginder, Jean D., 1966-1967 (Box-folder 141: 3)
    - Godo, Carlos, Conde de, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 141: 4)
    - Goldwater, Barry, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 141: 5)
    - Grasso, Ella, 1965 (Box-folder 141: 6)
    - Gray, Francis, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 141: 7)
    - Gray, James, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 141: 8)
    - Groves, Leslie R., 1966 (Box-folder 141: 9)
    - Guest, Winston, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 141: 10)
    - Gutierrez de Tobar, Javier, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 141: 11)
    - Hadley, Leila, 1967 (Box-folder 141: 12)
    - Hagerty, James, 1961 (Box-folder 141: 13)
    - Halsey, James, 1966 (Box-folder 141: 14)
    - Hammond, Paul, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 141: 15)
    - Hammons, Bernard, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 141: 16)
    - Harlow, A. Brooks, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 141: 17)
    - Hart, Luke, 1962 (Box-folder 141: 18)
    - Hart, Thomas C., 1962-1968 (Box-folder 141: 19)
    - Harvard Club of Southern Connecticut, 1962 (Box-folder 141: 20)
    - Harvard University, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 141: 21)
    - Hawkins, Richard, 1963 (Box-folder 141: 22)
    - Hays, Wayne, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 141: 23)
    - Henry, Isabella, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 141: 24)
    - Herter, Christian, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 141: 25)
    - Hess, Stephen, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 141: 26)
    - Hickling, R. A., 1961-1968 (Box-folder 141: 27)
    - Hill, Albert C., 1962-1966 (Box-folder 141: 28)
    - Hill, Robert C., 1961-1969 (Box-folder 141: 29)
    - Hillings, Pat, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 141: 30)
    - Hispanic Society of Chicago, 1967 (Box-folder 141: 31)
    - Hobart and William Smith College, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 141: 32)
    - Holtzmann, Fanny, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 141: 33-34)
    - Hoover, Mrs. Allan, 1962 (Box-folder 142: 1)
    - Hoover, Herbert, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 142: 2)
    - Hornbeck, Mrs. Stanley, 1967 (Box-folder 142: 3)
    - Hotchkis, Preston, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 142: 4)
    - Houston, Mr. and Mrs. Howard, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 142: 5)
    - Howard, Godfrey, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 142: 6)
    - Huang Hsi-lin, 1962 (Box-folder 142: 7)
    - Huang Shao-ku, 1962 (Box-folder 142: 8)
    - Hudson Institute, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 142: 9)
    - Humphrey, Hubert, 1965 (Box-folder 142: 10)
    - Hungarian Freedom Fighters' Foundation, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 142: 11)
    - Hurley, John, 1964-1967 (Box-folder 142: 12)
    - Institute for Advanced Study in the Theatre Arts, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 142: 13)
    - Instituto de Estudios Superiores de la Empresa, 1965 (Box-folder 142: 14)
    - Italian Alliance Clubs of North America, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 142: 15)
    - Ives, Colin C., 1961-1969 (Box-folder 142: 16)
    - Jackson, Donald, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 142: 17)
    - Jacobs, Albert C., 1967 (Box-folder 142: 18)
    - Janis, Martin, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 142: 19)
    - Jarrell, H. T., 1961-1965 (Box-folder 142: 20)
    - Jarvis, Fred, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 142: 21)
    - Javits, Benjamin, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 142: 22)
    - Javits, Jacob, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 142: 23)
    - Johns Hopkins University Press, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 142: 24)
    - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1965-1966 (Box-folder 142: 25)
    - Jones, Wilson T., 1968 (Box-folder 142: 26)
    - Judd, Walter, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 142: 27)
    - Junior Achievement, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 142: 28)
    - Kaufman, Draper, 1966 (Box-folder 142: 29)
    - Keating, Kenneth, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 142: 30)
    - Kelly, John C., 1962 (Box-folder 142: 31)
    - Kelly, Joseph, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 142: 32)
    - Kelly-Sanders-Hinkel, undated (Box-folder 142: 33)
    - Kennedy, Dana F., 1963-1968 (Box-folder 143: 1)
    - Kennedy, John F., 1961-1964 (Box-folder 143: 2)
    - Kessler, Philip, 1966 (Box-folder 143: 3)
    - Ketcham, Alan, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 143: 4)
    - Kilbourn, Orrin, 1965 (Box-folder 143: 5)
    - Kimball, John McKay, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 143: 6)
    - Kintner, William R., 1963-1965 (Box-folder 143: 7)
    - Kleindienst, Richard, 1968 (Box-folder 143: 8)
    - Knox Homes Corporation, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 143: 9)
    - Koopmans, Willem Cnoop, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 143: 10-11)
    - Kreisler, Edward, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 143: 12)
    - Krock, Arthur, 1966 (Box-folder 143: 13)
    - Krueger, Ernest, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 143: 14)
    - La Costa Magazine, 1968 (Box-folder 143: 15)
    - LaForgue, Rene, 1961 (Box-folder 143: 16)
    - Lall, Arthur, 1969 (Box-folder 143: 17)
    - Lamont, Mr. and Mrs. Gordon, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 143: 18-19)
    - Landy, Simon, 1962 (Box-folder 143: 20)
    - Langner, Lawrence, 1961 (Box-folder 143: 21)
    - LaPorte-Cholet, A. M., 1966 (Box-folder 143: 22)
    - LaRoche, Chester, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 143: 23)
    - League of Women Voters, 1965 (Box-folder 143: 24)
    - Lebedeff, Vera, 1968 (Box-folder 143: 25)
    - Leitman, Henri, 1963 (Box-folder 144: 1)
    - Lemaire, Louis, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 144: 2)
    - LeMay, Curtis E., 1965 (Box-folder 144: 3)
    - Levy, Herman, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 144: 4)
    - Lewis, Hobart, 1968 (Box-folder 144: 5)
    - Lewis, Wolfram, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 144: 6)
    - Lighton, Lewis, 1962 (Box-folder 144: 7)
    - Lindsay, John, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 144: 8)
    - Littauer, Helen, 1965 (Box-folder 144: 9)
    - Lodge, Beatrice, 1966 (Box-folder 144: 10)
    - Lodge, Francesca, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 144: 11-12)
    - Lodge, George Cabot, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 144: 13)
    - Lodge, Henry Cabot, Jr., 1961-1969 (Box-folder 144: 14-17)
    - Lodge, Henry Sears, 1963 (Box-folder 144: 18)
    - Lodge, Mrs. John Ellerton, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 144: 19)
    - Loeb, William, 1967-1968 (Box-folder 144: 20)
    - Logan, John, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 144: 21)
    - Longworth, Alice Roosevelt, 1969 (Box-folder 144: 22)
    - Loomis, Pat, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 145: 1)
    - Loy, Thomas, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 145: 2)
    - Luce, Clare Boothe, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 145: 3)
    - Luce, Henry, 1961 (Box-folder 145: 4)
    - Luce, Stephan, 1961 (Box-folder 145: 5)
    - Luna Iglesias, Alejandro, 1961 (Box-folder 145: 6)
    - Lupton, John, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 145: 7)
    - Luque, Jesus, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 145: 8)
    - McAllister, Ken, 1965 (Box-folder 145: 9)
    - MacArthur, Douglas, 1964 (Box-folder 145: 10)
    - MacArthur, Helen Hayes, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 145: 11)
    - Macauley, Thurston, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 145: 12)
    - Macaya, Ignacio, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 145: 13)
    - Macaya, Juan, 1961 (Box-folder 145: 14)
    - McBride, Robert, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 145: 15)
    - McCall, Tom, 1967 (Box-folder 145: 16)
    - McEvoy, Joseph F., 1963-1969 (Box-folder 145: 17)
    - McKee, Michael, 1966 (Box-folder 145: 18)
    - MacKinnon, George E., 1969 (Box-folder 145: 19)
    - McNeil, Thomas, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 145: 20)
    - MacVeagh, Charlton, 1962-1963 (Box-folder 145: 21)
    - Madariaga, Juan Jose de, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 145: 22-23)
    - Marcus, James and Lily (Lodge), 1963-1967 (Box-folder 145: 24)
    - Marcus, Stanley, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 145: 25)
    - Mark Twain Journal, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 145: 26)
    - Marshall, Charles, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 145: 27)
    - Marsilius, Newman, 1964 (Box-folder 145: 28)
    - Martin, Joseph W., Jr., 1962 (Box-folder 145: 29)
    - Martin Gamero, Adolfo, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 145: 30)
    - Martin, Tony, 1963 (Box-folder 145: 31)
    - Mary Baldwin College, 1968 (Box-folder 145: 32)
    - Mason, Anne, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 145: 33)
    - Maury, Reuben, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 145: 34)
    - Mawson, Leon, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 146: 1)
    - May, Ed, 1968 (Box-folder 146: 2)
    - Mayalde, Conde de, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 146: 3)
    - Meek, Samuel, 1966 (Box-folder 146: 4)
    - Merchant, Livingston, 1965 (Box-folder 146: 5)
    - Merry del Val, Alfonso, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 146: 6)
    - Meskill, Thomas, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 146: 7)
    - Michel, Robert, 1964-1968 (Box-folder 146: 8)
    - Milbank, Jeremiah, 1963-1969 (Box-folder 146: 9)
    - Miller, William E., 1963-1964 (Box-folder 146: 10)
    - Miller, William J., 1964-1966 (Box-folder 146: 11)
    - Minot, William A. G., 1962-1967 (Box-folder 146: 12)
    - Mitchell, John N., 1968 (Box-folder 146: 13)
    - Moats, Alice, 1969 (Box-folder 146: 14)
    - Monterey Institute of Foreign Studies, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 146: 15)
    - Montgomery, Douglass, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 146: 16)
    - Montgomery, Ruth, 1964-1966 (Box-folder 146: 17)
    - Moreland, Andrew, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 146: 18)
    - Morgan, John, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 146: 19)
    - Morgantina, 1965 (Box-folder 146: 20)
    - Morris, Dubois, Jr., 1967 (Box-folder 146: 21)
    - Morris, Edgar, 1966 (Box-folder 146: 22)
    - Morse, Harry, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 146: 23)
    - Morton, Thruston, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 146: 24)
    - Mott, Jordon, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 146: 25)
    - Mulcahy, Leo, 1965-1967 (Box-folder 146: 26)
    - Mullen, Robert, 1965 (Box-folder 146: 27)
    - Mundt, Karl, 1967 (Box-folder 146: 28)
    - Munoz, Antonio, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 146: 29)
    - Muns, Alejandro de, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 146: 30)
    - Murphy, George, 1965 (Box-folder 146: 31)
    - Murphy, Robert, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 146: 32)
    - Nagler, Jerry, 1963 (Box-folder 147: 1)
    - Napper, Bernice, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 147: 2)
    - Nash, E. C., 1961-1969 (Box-folder 147: 3)
    - National Audobon Society, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 147: 4)
    - National Conference of Christians and Jews, 1961-1962 (Box-folder 147: 5)
    - National Petroleum Corporation, 1966 (Box-folder 147: 6)
    - National Strategy Information Center, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 147: 7)
    - Neff, John, 1967 (Box-folder 147: 8)
    - Negro College Fund, 1966 (Box-folder 147: 9)
    - Neiman, Nelson, 1968 (Box-folder 147: 10)
    - New York Times, 1967 (Box-folder 147: 11)
    - Ni Yue-si, 1962 (Box-folder 147: 12)
    - Nichols, William I., 1961-1969 (Box-folder 147: 13)
    - Nixon, Catherine, 1963 (Box-folder 147: 14)
    - Nixon, Richard M., 1963-1969 (Box-folder 147: 15)
    - Noel, Sterling, 1965-1966 (Box-folder 147: 16)
    - Nolan, James, 1965 (Box-folder 147: 17)
    - Norton, Josiah, 1968 (Box-folder 147: 18)
    - Norton, Julian, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 147: 19)
    - Norwalk Club, 1968 (Box-folder 147: 20)
    - Nyaradi, Nicholas, 1965-1969 (Box-folder 147: 21)
    - Oakes, George W., 1965 (Box-folder 147: 22)
    - Oakie, Jack, 1962-1965 (Box-folder 147: 23)
    - O'Brien, Edmund, 1963-1966 (Box-folder 147: 24)
    - O'Donnell, Gladys, 1966-1969 (Box-folder 147: 25)
    - Olano, Luis de, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 147: 26)
    - Olmstead, Alan, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 147: 27)
    - Oram, Harold, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 147: 28)
    - Orkin, William, 1966 (Box-folder 148: 1)
    - Orlandini, Edward, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 148: 2)
    - Orleans y Borbon, Alfonso de, 1962 (Box-folder 148: 3)
    - Oyarzabal, Antonio and Beatrice (Lodge), 1961-1969 (Box-folder 148: 4-5)
    - Oyarzabal y Velarde, Alberto, 1961 (Box-folder 148: 6)
    - Pabst, Robert, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 148: 7)
    - Parr, Charles, 1962 (Box-folder 148: 8)
    - Pastor, Lucy, 1967 (Box-folder 148: 9)
    - Patterson, Richard C., Jr., 1961 (Box-folder 148: 10)
    - Pawley, William D., 1963-1968 (Box-folder 148: 11)
      Includes Pawley's "A Brief History of the Flying Tigers" and Charles F. Romanus and Riley Sunderland's "Stilwell's Mission to China."
    - Pell, Mrs. John, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 148: 12)
    - Pell, Robert, 1962 (Box-folder 148: 13)
    - Pennsylvania Council of Republican Women, 1961 (Box-folder 148: 14)
    - Pereira, Pedro T., 1961-1967 (Box-folder 148: 15)
    - Peterson, Arthur, 1966 (Box-folder 148: 16)
    - Peterson, Oscar, 1963 (Box-folder 148: 17)
    - Pinney, A. Searle, 1964 (Box-folder 148: 18)
    - Ploeser, Walter, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 148: 19)
    - Pope, Frederick, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 148: 20)
    - Popham, John M., 1966-1969 (Box-folder 148: 21)
    - Potts, Mary, 1963-1964 (Box-folder 148: 22)
    - Powell, Wesley, 1962 (Box-folder 148: 23)
    - Presbrey, Martha Rountree, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 148: 24)
    - Previdi, John, 1966-1968 (Box-folder 148: 25)
    - Pryor, Samuel, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 148: 26)
    - Quincy, Edmund, 1962 (Box-folder 148: 27)
    - Quintanilla, Aline, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 148: 28)
    - Rabb, Maxwell, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 148: 29)
    - Raymond, Allen, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 148: 30)
    - Raymond, Gene, 1965 (Box-folder 148: 31)
    - Reig Reig, A. Adolfo, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 148: 32)
    - Reincke, Frederick, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 148: 33)
    - Reischauer, Edwin, 1966 (Box-folder 148: 34)
    - Reitemeyer, John, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 148: 35)
    - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1962 (Box-folder 149: 1)
    - Republican National Committee, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 149: 2)
    - Republican Women of Westport, 1968 (Box-folder 149: 3)
    - Republican Women's Association, 1968 (Box-folder 149: 4)
    - Reynolds, Reginald, 1963-1968 (Box-folder 149: 5)
    - Ribicoff, Abraham, 1965 (Box-folder 149: 6)
    - Rideout, George M., 1965 (Box-folder 149: 7)
    - Riesel, Victor, 1962-1964 (Box-folder 149: 8)
    - Rimanoczy, Richard, 1965 (Box-folder 149: 9)
    - Ripon Society, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 149: 10)
    - Robert Taft Institute of Government, 1967 (Box-folder 149: 11)
    - Rockefeller, Nelson, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 149: 12)
    - Rockefeller, Winthrop, 1967 (Box-folder 149: 13)
    - Rodgers, Churchill, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 149: 14)
    - Roebling, Mary, 1967 (Box-folder 149: 15)
    - Rogers, Willard, 1962 (Box-folder 149: 16)
    - Roland, Robert, 1965 (Box-folder 149: 17)
    - Roosevelt, Archibald, 1962 (Box-folder 149: 18)
    - Roots, John McCook, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 149: 19)
    - Rosen, Lucie, 1964 (Box-folder 149: 20)
    - Ross, Norman P., 1962 (Box-folder 149: 21)
    - Roth, Philip, 1963 (Box-folder 149: 22)
    - Routh, Robert, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 149: 23)
    - Ruiz-Morales, Jose, 1967 (Box-folder 149: 24)
    - Rusk, Dean, 1965 (Box-folder 149: 25)
    - Ryan, Cornelius, 1969 (Box-folder 149: 26)
    - Ryan, Frank, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 149: 27)
    - Rysdyk, Frank, 1968 (Box-folder 149: 28)
    - Ryskind, Allan, 1967 (Box-folder 149: 29)
    - Sachar, Louis, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 149: 30)
    - Sacksteder, Fred, Jr., 1961-1968 (Box-folder 149: 31)
    - Sadlak, Antoni, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 149: 32)
    - Salet, Eugene, 1965 (Box-folder 149: 33)
    - Salles, Edouard, 1963-1965 (Box-folder 149: 34)
    - Sampsell, Margaret, 1963-1967 (Box-folder 149: 35)
    - Sampsell, Marshall, 1968-1969 (Box-folder 149: 36)
    - Sangiovanni, William, 1964-1969 (Box-folder 150: 1)
    - Sanz-Briz, Angel, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 150: 2)
    - Savitt, Max, 1961-1964 (Box-folder 150: 3)
    - Saxe, Thomas, 1962-1968 (Box-folder 150: 4)
    - Scalise, Eugene, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 150: 5)
    - Schoolboys Abroad Program, 1965-1968 (Box-folder 150: 6)
    - Schwolsky, Harry, 1968 (Box-folder 150: 7)
    - Scott, Hugh, 1961 (Box-folder 150: 8)
    - Scranton, William, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 150: 9)
    - Seely-Brown, Horace, 1962 (Box-folder 150: 10)
    - Senni, Livio, 1962 (Box-folder 150: 11)
    - Shakespeare, Frank, 1969 (Box-folder 150: 12)
    - Shankel, James E., 1962-1965 (Box-folder 150: 13)
    - Shannon, James, 1965 (Box-folder 150: 14)
    - Shea, Frank, 1962 (Box-folder 150: 15)
    - Sheen, Fulton J., 1961 (Box-folder 150: 16)
    - Sherwell, G. Butler, 1961 (Box-folder 150: 17)
    - Shull, Frederick, 1962 (Box-folder 150: 18)
    - Sibal, Abner W., 1962-1966 (Box-folder 150: 19)
    - Sidor, Walter, 1968 (Box-folder 150: 20)
    - Sikorsky, Igor, 1966 (Box-folder 150: 21)
    - Simon, Caroline, 1963 (Box-folder 150: 22)
    - Sinon, Frank A., 1963-1965 (Box-folder 150: 23)
    - Smedberg, William, 1969 (Box-folder 150: 24)
    - Smith, Kingsbury, 1964 (Box-folder 150: 25)
    - Smith, Margaret Chase, 1966 (Box-folder 150: 26)
    - Smith, Truman, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 150: 27)
    - Smith, William B., 1966 (Box-folder 150: 28)
    - Society of Mayflower Descendants, 1965 (Box-folder 150: 29)
    - Society of Naval Architects and Marine Engineers, 1968 (Box-folder 150: 30)
    - Sonneville, Pierre, 1967 (Box-folder 150: 31)
    - Spanish Institute, 1963 (Box-folder 150: 32)
    - Speakes, Charme, 1965 (Box-folder 150: 33)
    - Speiden, J. G. F., 1962-1969 (Box-folder 150: 34)
    - Spellman, Francis Cardinal, 1965 (Box-folder 150: 35)
    - Steele, Bernard, 1961-1967 (Box-folder 150: 36)
    - Stevens, John G., 1965-1967 (Box-folder 150: 37)
    - Stevens, Peter, 1966 (Box-folder 150: 38)
    - Stevens, Ronald, 1966 (Box-folder 150: 39)
    - Stockwell, Jane, 1964-1965 (Box-folder 151: 1)
    - Strausz-Hupe, Robert, 1964 (Box-folder 151: 2)
    - Streel, Helena (Lodge) de, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 151: 3)
    - Stroud, Joan, 1967-1969 (Box-folder 151: 4)
    - Sueca, Belen, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 151: 5)
    - Suffield Republican Women's Club, 1962 (Box-folder 151: 6)
    - Sullivan, Peter, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 151: 7)
    - Swann, A. K., 1966 (Box-folder 151: 8)
    - Tassie, Michael, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 151: 9)
    - Taylor and Schlanger, 1962-1969 (Box-folder 151: 10)
    - Tennyson, Paule, 1967 (Box-folder 151: 11)
    - Thaw, Lawrence, 1961-1965 (Box-folder 151: 12)
    - Thayer, Walter, 1962-1967 (Box-folder 151: 13)
    - Thomas, Richard, 1966 (Box-folder 151: 14)
    - Thorne, Bob, 1962 (Box-folder 151: 15)
    - Thornton, Dan, 1963 (Box-folder 151: 16)
    - Tierney, John, 1961-1963 (Box-folder 151: 17)
    - Todd, Webster, 1965 (Box-folder 151: 18)
    - Tone, Aileen, 1965 April (Box-folder 151: 19)
    - Touche, Armand, 1961-1968 (Box-folder 151: 20)
    - Town and Country Club, 1961 (Box-folder 151: 21)
    - Trohan, Walter, 1961-1969 (Box-folder 151: 22)
    - Truth About Cuba Committee, 1968 (Box-folder 151: 23)
    - Tunney, Gene, 1961-1966 (Box-folder 151: 24)
    - Tutoli, Benidict, 1965 (Box-folder 151: 25)
    - Tyng, Lila, 1962-1966 (Box-folder 151: 26)